(Howard:)Tomato, tomahto.
The important thing is she's dead.
(Bernadette:)Hey, so how come you two
didn't move in together?
(Leonard:)This guy wanted
a place of his own
(Leonard:)because he was sure he was
gonna be a ladies' man.
(Raj:)Yeah, I was wrong.
(Raj:)But I do think you and I
would have had a great time.
(Raj:)Come on, Leonard, dinner.
(Sheldon:)Coming.
(Raj:)Hang on.
(Leonard:)Why would I be fat?
(Raj:)You'd have no girlfriend
to see you naked,
(Raj:)you'd try to fill the void
with food,
(Raj:)and I'm an enabler who once
deep-fried a pancake.
(Leonard:)Why can't you be fat too?
(Fat Leonard:)What do you want
to do for dessert?
(Fat Raj:)I think there's still
half a cake from breakfast.